<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TFAbout</string>

    <string name="title_section1">THE TEAM</string>
    <string name="title_section2">CHANGELOG</string>
    <string name="title_section3">LINKS</string>
    <!-- Modo swipe-->
    <string name="title_activity_about_swipe">ROMS NAME</string>

    <!-- Modo drawer-->
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_item_list">Items</string>
    <string name="title_item_detail">Item Detail</string>


    <string name="urlWeb">http://www.tfandroid.es</string>
    <string name="urlFacebook">https://www.facebook.com/TeamForceGroup</string>
    <string name="urlGoogle">https://plus.google.com/u/0/101598355663549822553/posts</string>
    <string name="urlRss">http://tfandroid.es/feed/</string>
    <string name="urlTwitter">https://twitter.com/TeamForceGroup</string>
    <string name="urlYoutube">http://www.youtube.com/user/TeamForceGroup</string>

    <string name="team">
    Welcome to Team Force:\n\n

In Team Force, we are a united group of Android enthusiasts can offer our knowledge and work focused on the optimization and capacity based on Android ROMS, from time to Jiayu.\n\n

What we can offer is a large amount and quality made ​​and thoroughly tested ROMS tried to polish the details that make the difference.\n\n

You will also find videos, reviews, tutorials to make the simplest possible installation and upgrade processes and to resolve any doubts you may have.\n\n

We work very closely with the developer and manufacturer of terminals Jiayu, this allows us to have exclusive authentic as the source code for the various terminals, which can bring changes ROMS, Kernel… in other sites is currently not possible to obtain.\n\n

Again welcome you and hope you find your place in Team Force and everything you expected when you bought your Jiayu terminal.\n\n

As you can read our current work is aimed at Jiayu terminals, in the future it plans to develop other models and manufacturers.\n\n

Right now what we are Team Force the following:\n\n

Development: Fraggel, Erfae and Newton\n

Design: Menkato\n

Web: Siulwon\n

Social Network: Siulwon\n

Content: Borx\n

Reviews:\n

International Manager:\n

And Betatesters Group\n
    </string>

</resources>
